[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
That's enough, Bok!
Sianong!
It's not too late for Chiara.
Chiara isn't the one who's responsible for all of this.
It's Vicky.
You two go to Italy!
I'm tired.
Bok!
Sianong!
I wish he had given us a chance to help him.
But that doesn't justify betraying us.
He was also a victim of a system
that made him believe he had no other choice.
We need to bring down the system
that creates people like him.
And the Concordat.
-Definitely Italy. -Italy?
So, what are you going to do in Italy?
I have some friends there too.
The Castellanis.
One day, I'll take you there.
Now I know why in Italy.
-Why? -Sianong has friends there.
Castellani?
If that's Sianong's last clue to us,
those are the people he wants us to find.
Mom.
Want to go shopping?
My in-law texted.
Tess.
It's like
she's sensing something
about what happened.
About what happened between you and Mikoy.
What did she say?
You know that?
You're right.
So what did you reply?
What?
I just hearted it, Chiara,
because I didn't know what to say.
I might say the wrong thing. Better not.
Mama Yaya.
Rahmboy.
Chiara.
Sianong…
He's gone.
He was careless.
That's how the agency caught him.
They chased him,
and while he was trying to escape,
he got into an accident.
Human life is so fragile
in this world of ours.
Haven't you gotten used to it?
I'm used to it.
Well, is this going to be a problem?
No.
He can't talk now, so there won't be.
Honestly, I thought about it too.
It's better that Sianong is gone
because I know he was the one who hated Mikoy the most.
Now that he's gone,
Mikoy is safer.
Isn't that what you wanted?
How is he?
Mikoy?
He's still alive.
he has no way of getting to you anymore.
That's probably for the best.
With everything that's happening,
he may be moving on too.
the Castellani family was first known for their jewelry.
their family business was at risk.
And eventually, they slowly integrated themselves into the mafia world,
just to survive.
And it seems like it all paid off
because currently, the new generation of Castellanis
is the biggest threat to the Concordat's leadership.
Well, aside from looking like models,
the Castellanis certainly have a strong presence.
Appeal isn't all they have.
the Castellanis are currently negotiating with Chiara.
Mom, Chiara, I'll go ahead.
Okay, dear.
Jeez.
They rejected our counteroffer again.
Yes, Chiara.
They still won't agree.
They're so conniving.
Why don't they want to come to an agreement?
What do they really want?
Your position, of course, dear.
Before you took over, what the Castellanis wanted
was to lead and control the Concordat.
But that didn't happen.
So they're extremely bitter about it.
So they're causing trouble
just because they can't accept that I'm now the leader of the Concordat?
Guys are indeed hard to understand.
So stressful.
So they're not fans of Chiara's leadership?
I think it's not just because the Castellanis have appeal or influence.
You're right, Dara.
In fact, that's the trend these days.
Can I use the phone?
Sure, sir.
No one's really using it anymore.
Everyone just chats now.
Thanks.
I know they are in Italy.
But Italy is too big, and I don't have enough time.
If I have to know something as soon as possible,
then tell me now.
What's this?
You're making a move on your own?
And who were you talking to?
My asset.
Wow.
And since when did you have an asset?
That's not important anymore, Alex.
What do you mean, it's not?
Are you sure about this?
And who is this person?
They might get you into trouble.
Just leave me alone, Alex. I know what I'm doing.
Just let me have this one.
It's safer if you don't know who they are.
What matters is I can reach him through the landline,
and he gives me vital information.
‎Oh.
What's the problem?
-What happened? -What happened?
What happened? Why?
What did they say?
they want to meet me.
Finally, they're willing to talk.
What's so good about it?
What if they have a different agenda?
What if-- What if they suddenly…
Ambush! What if they ambush us?
It's dangerous, dear. Don't do it!
You're being dramatic.
You're being way too negative. It's just a meeting, dear.
Dear, you know I never lie to you.
You know those Castellanis, they are cunning.
We're going to prepare.
They're cunning? That's their reputation.
We won't back out.
Italy is huge.
Where in Italy?
But are you sure Chiara Valtrovi will go?
Yes, Mikoy.
Isn't it dangerous for Chiara
to meet with the Castellanis?
Rahmboy, dear.
You go with Chiara,
so the Castellanis can see that we're training
new generation of mafia leaders just like them.
That's why the Moravianos don't take you seriously,
if you're going to be this cowardly, Viktor!
I'm the one who thinks things through.
Between the two of us, I'm the one who takes action.
You're so funny, you know that?
You have no right to take action or make decisions.
You're just sticking your nose in all this.
Oh, I'm just sticking my nose in?
You rich and powerful people,
you think you have this huge illusion
that you're the ones who make everything happen.
But if it weren't for us poor people
doing the work for you,
you'd have nothing!
We're just wasting time because you two keep arguing.
Rahmboy, you're coming with me.
Are you telling me, Mikoy, that you're getting all of this
from your secret asset?
There you go again.
How can you say that your intel is legit?
We don't even know who your asset is.
You have a point, sir.
We just got a little excited about the information he has.
I'm skeptical too, just like you.
See? You get it now?
Even though Chiara is now the leader of the Concordat,
she wouldn't risk her life or the lives of her people
to meet with a group
that clearly doesn't want her leading them.
With all due respect, sir,
you don't know Chiara.
You don't understand her.
Dear.
Do not go, please.
Remember,
He's right, dear.
Listen to your father.
Whatever happened between Chiara and me,
we still have a history.
And that's my advantage over all of you.
I'm sorry my asset is top secret.
Maybe in time, you'll understand why.
She's different.
She wants every move she makes to make a statement.
Especially now that she's the leader of the Concordat.
She needs to prove through her actions
But things are different now.
What would they think of me?
but the other Concordat groups as well.
I'm sure all of them are waiting
you're saying that
Chiara is really going to Italy?
I have a strong feeling she is, sir.
Well, if that's the case,
then all we have to do is wait for Chiara Valtrovi
when she goes to Italy.
Exactly!
This is our golden window.
How can we make sure Chiara will cooperate with us?
Exactly, Mikoy.
What if Chiara refuses to cooperate?
Or refuses to be caught.
What?
You'll be playing cat and mouse in Italy.
Or worse, it'll be catch me if you can all over Europe.
Impossible.
We don't have the budget for that.
Back in Hong Kong,
even though you tried to escape from us,
you still cooperated with us even while the two of you were together.
You had an agreement, and eventually,
you ended up with very important information
in exchange for a day.
she won't back down.
She managed to escape our law enforcement agency here.
And it seems impossible
that we can persuade her to come back to our country.
Who came up with the idea of going to Italy
to shake hands with criminals?
Mikoy.
Didn't we agree that we're there to get Chiara Valtrovi?
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Me? Of course, I'm more than okay.
I may endure some body pains,
but at least I've got plenty of tricks up my sleeve.
Right? Thanks to you.
That's the spirit.
That's the fighting spirit I want to see.
But tell me something, Rahmboy.
Can I trust you?
Trust?
Me?
Of course!
You really doubt me now?
I heard that
you've been having second thoughts.
That you're not fully committed.
Is that true?
Chiara.
I'm fully committed.
There are probably still things I need to learn, but…
I'm ready.
And remember this.
We're on the same side.
You can count on me, Chiara.
But I want you to remember this too.
I'm on your side.
If you have any doubts, it's better to tell me.
Because from now on,
you're my responsibility.
Okay.
But my gut feel tells me that this isn't an ordinary mission.
We're going to a place
where the most powerful mafia are gathering for a meeting.
One mistake there,
and we're all dead.
In the mafia life, there's always one problem after another.
Look at me.
La Morte Bianca raised me and trained me.
But…
I still managed to stand against her.
For now, let's focus on the Castellanis.
We know how cunning they are. So let's be careful.
You've been staring into space for a while now.
I was just thinking about your brother.
But you know, no matter how heavy the burden is,
I'm sure he'll get through all of it.
Why don't we show him that we're here, that we support him?
I have an idea.
Hello, Captain Pepe.
I was hoping to ask you a favor.